Gerda Jechsmayr

805 SW Palatine St, Portland OR 97219 gerda.jechsmayr @ gmail.com (503) 734-8276

Summary

A passionate and creative problem-solver with a proven record of delivering results thru logical solutions. I'm a "roll-up-my-sleeves" kind of person with experience in entrepreneurial startup businesses.

IT Skills

MS Office, SAP GL, SAP LOGISTICS, SAP SALES, SAP ACCOUNTING, Lotus Notes, Remedy, caps, Stacc, KEA, Outlook, VM 7, CAD, various FM programs (Aperture, Speedikon ...), Windows XP, MAC, iPad,

Professional Experience

ARWAG residential neighborhoods 1030 Vienna 2002 - 2009
 Facility Manager
 Managed all aspects of residential properties. Providing customer support, tracking regular maintenance, cleaning and security. Reviewing and selecting contractor bid

regular maintenance, cleaning and security. Reviewing and selecting contractor bids for repairs, placing orders and conducting final inspections. Oversaw liability cases and followed thru on general administrative work.

Interxion Telecom Service GmbH, 1210 Vienna
 2000 - 2001

 Facility Manager
 Oversaw and managed build-outs and alterations to server rooms (+10,000 sq. ft.).

 Actively engaged in purchasing decisions, negotiations as well as relocation and furnishing needs. Managed all facets of the facilities from security and access control.

furnishing needs. Managed all facets of the facilities from security and access controls to directing fiber optic placements. Lead the planning and catering of events as well as cleaning and customer service.

between Sales, Logistics and Warehouse.

Gerda Jechsmayr

Accounting Department

1996 - 1998

Implemented SAP in financial accounting. Oversaw all facility agendas. Managed all contracts with cell towers. Issued payments to landowners.

ÖAR Regional Consulting, 1130 Vienna
 1994 - 1996

 Handled the accounting responsibilities from bookkeeping, tracking travel expenses to purchasing office materials. Oversaw facility management, assisted with front desk and provided project support to engineers.

Education

2005 Universitaet Bodenkultur Vienna attended

Other coursework

2003	English, web design HTML
2000 - 2001	Facility manager training courses and project training at Wifi Vienna
1996	Hospitality qualification examination at Wifi Vienna
1995 - 1996	Comprehensive Business Secretary training at Wifi Vienna

Various other training

Project Management / Advisory Group Neuwaldegg Women in Management / IIR Staff conversations, PPRESAL TRAINING / ONE Leadership, communication and motivation / MDI-SPIDI Understanding GSM / ONE English for the telecom sector / ONE Dale Carnegie Training Communications French, University of Dijon, France SAP Key user

Languages

English German